snowmagazine.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy policy

PRIVACY POLICY

As the publishers of snowmagazine.com and Snow Magazine, Double A Media Ltd is committed to respecting the privacy of its users. However, we do collect and use various bits of information about you through your use of this website, and this policy sets out the basis on which your personal data will be collected, stored and processed. The data collector for this website is Double A Media Ltd., with its registered office at 97 Avondale Road, Mortlake, London, SW14 8PU. Please note that this policy only addresses our activities, and other sites to which this website links may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.

1\. Collection

We shall ask you to supply personal information (data) to us in the following circumstances:

(a) when you wish to become a registered user of this website (www.snowmagazine.com) and/or  
(b) when you wish to buy or utilise any of our products or services.

2\. Information

The personal data that we shall ask you to supply shall include the following:

(a) your name, address, and email address; and  
(b) your postcode and telephone number; and  
(c) (if you make purchases) your credit card or other financial or payment details.

We may also ask you to provide other personal data to us for particular purposes, such as supplying our products or services to you. In each case it will be your decision as to whether you supply us with the information in question or not.

3\. Use of your personal information

We shall only use your personal data for the following purposes where applicable:

(a) to identify you as a registered user of our website and to allow you to post messages on our forum;  
(b) to provide you with products and services (which may include products and services that we supply in association with other businesses);   
(c) to process any applicable payments from you;  
(d) to send you information regarding our products and services with your consent;  
(e) to send you information regarding the products and services of other businesses with your consent;  
(f) to notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions from time to time;  
(g) for our own internal purposes in connection with risk control, resolving consumer disputes; and  
(h) for producing statistics and other information relating to our business and the users of our website.

You may at any time revoke your consent to us contacting you for the purposes noted in (d) and (e) above by contacting us at [here](http://snowmagazine.com/component/contact/contact/12-contacts/1-snowmagazinecom), or by unsubscribing from our email mailing lists by following the procedure set out in any of the relevant emails that we send you.

General Information

Any information or statistics relating to our business that we disclose to others shall not identify you personally. We may, for example, perform statistical analyses of the behaviour of the users of our website in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site and to tell advertisers how many users of our website have seen or "clicked" their advertising banners. This information, and any other general information about our users that we share with advertisers and other partners, will not disclose personal information about you.

4\. Disclosure of your personal information

We shall only disclose your personal data to other people in the following circumstances:

(a) to verify and process any payment instructions that you give us when you order any of our products or services;  
(b) to other businesses, when we are providing products or services to you in association with those businesses (see 3(b) above);  
(c) to prepare or send any communications to you, or to assist us in connection with any of our administrative or business functions, or in the provision of any of our products or our services to you;   
(d) to verify your credit worthiness or financial circumstances, for the purpose of making credit decisions, and in connection with fraud prevention and tracing debtors; and   
(e) if we are asked to do by any legal or regulatory authority, or if we believe that it would be proper to do so in connection with any legal or regulatory matter.

Unless they are already legally bound to keep your personal data confidential, we shall enter into agreements with anyone to whom we disclose your personal data under (a), (b), (c) and (d) above obliging them to keep your personal data confidential.

5\. Sale and supply

We shall comply with the following restrictions in relation to your personal information.

(a) We shall not sell your personal data to anyone else, though with your permission we may rent it for limited use or contact you by post or email on behalf of other carefully selected companies. You can switch your permission on and off on your 'My Details' page.  
(b) Subject to the exception in point 4(e) above, we shall not supply your personal data to anyone else so that they can use it for their own purposes.

6\. Security of your personal information

We shall take steps to ensure that your personal data is kept reasonably secure whilst it is in our possession, and your credit card details will only be stored and transmitted by us in an encrypted form.

7\. Other information that we collect

When you visit our site we may log IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.

We may collect information about your viewing habits when you visit our website through your IP address and by using cookies and other web tools in the following ways.

(a) Cookies. A "cookie" is a small electronic file that collects information when someone visits a website. A cookie can identify the pages that are being viewed, and this can assist us to select the pages that the viewer sees. Some cookies only exist whilst viewers are online, but "persistent" cookies - which are not session-based - remain on the viewer's computer, so that he or she can be recognised as a previous visitor when he or she next visits our website. This information allows us to collect information about a viewer's browsing habits, and this can be useful in assisting us to monitor and improve our services. We do not store sensitive information such as account numbers or passwords in "persistent" cookies, and cookies, in themselves, do not contain enough information to identify you. You will only acquire a personal identity in relation to your browsing habits after you have formally provide us with your personal data for the purposes outlined in point 3 above.  
(b) GIF and other web tools. In addition to using cookies, we might also use GIFs and other web tools to collect information about your browsing activities. In this respect the information that is provided is similar to the information supplied by cookies, and we use it for the same purposes. Information that we automatically collect and analyse about you may include: the Internet Protocol (IP) address that you use to connect your computer to the Internet; your login, email address, and password; the computer and connection information relating to you (such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform); your purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from this website (including date and time); and any items you viewed or searched for. Any information that we acquire about you using cookies, GIFs or other web tools, or which we collect in any other way is subject to the same restrictions and conditions as any of the more formal personal data we collect about you.

We have implemented Google Analytics feature; Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.  
you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads

NOTE. Some of the advertisements on our website may contain cookies, GIFs, or other web tools that are set by other people such as advertising agencies, or the businesses to which the advertisements in question relate. We do not have access to any information that might be collected in this way, and (if you are concerned) you should contact the advertiser for more information.

8\. Amendments, cancellation, and contact us

At your request we shall make any amendments that you stipulate to the personal data that you have supplied us with. If you require it we shall also remove your name and personal data from our database. This shall be on the basis that you shall be deemed to have cancelled any contract or licence you may have had with us that the personal data in question related to, and (as we shall not have been at fault in those circumstances) you shall not be entitled to any compensation or refunds in relation to the cancellation of the applicable contract or licence.

Please contact us at [here](http://snowmagazine.com/component/contact/contact/12-contacts/1-snowmagazinecom) in relation to the matters to which this point 7 relates, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy.

 **APP Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how Double A Media Ltd. uses and protects any information that you give Double A Media Ltd. when you use our apps.

Double A Media Ltd. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using the apps, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Double A Media Ltd. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from [date].

What we collect  
We may collect the following information:

name and job title  
contact information including email address  
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

What we do with the information we gather We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

Internal record keeping.

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the Apps according to your interests.

 **Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
 ****  
 **Links to other websites**  
Our Apps may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our App, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the App, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at the address below, or by using the [contact us](http://snowmagazine.com/contact-us) form.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Data Controller, Double A Media Ltd, 97 Avondale Road. Mortlake, London, SW14 8PU.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

2012 © Double A Media Ltd Ltd. All rights reserved. Our terms and conditions

This Privacy Policy has been prepared to meet the requirements of the UK's Data Protection Act 1998, and that Act only relates to the collection, protection, disclosure and use of personal data belonging to living individuals. It does not relate to data regarding companies and other non-living entities, although the general principles regarding our collection and use of data is broadly the same irrespective of whether the users of our website are living individuals or not.

Double A Media LTD is a company incorporated in England and Wales under Company Number 06936445.  
Registered Office: 97 Avondale Road, Mortlake, London, SW14 8PU
